<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ankit Hans</title><link>https://ankithans.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Ankit Hans</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ankithans.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Halfway in Google Summer of Code</title><link>https://ankithans.github.io/posts/2021/07/halfway-in-google-summer-of-code/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ankithans.github.io/posts/2021/07/halfway-in-google-summer-of-code/</guid><description>How is GSoC going? My experience with Google Summer of Code and my organisation Aerogear(JBoss) has been so great till now, learning new things everyday has really became a part of my life.
It has been almost 2 months since I got into the program, but it feels like tomorrow! When I started contributing or writing proposal, I was like zero in golang, but comparing then and now, it&amp;rsquo;s different. In this journey I got to know about some great concepts in golang and again many yet to be explored!</description></item><item><title>GSoC'21 journey begins</title><link>https://ankithans.github.io/posts/2021/06/gsoc21-journey-begins/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ankithans.github.io/posts/2021/06/gsoc21-journey-begins/</guid><description>Get started with open-source I myself started with opensource in end of the year 2020. Explored a lot of organizations, according to my interest and tech-stack. And I got a list of 20+ orgs, so I took my time, may be a week and gone through the projects of all of them. Then finally I found LibreHealth and JBoss.
I started my opensource journey with LibreHealth. The project was Cost of Care Application which aims to to provide patient friendly costs of care, to help patients get better cost estimates for medical procedures of Hospitals.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://ankithans.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ankithans.github.io/about/</guid><description>Hi 👋, I am Ankit Hans I am a ✨ Full Stack Developer, 💻 Open Source enthusiast and I love building great and cool stuffs for the community.
🙏 Welcome to my Blog, Here I share my experiences with Software Developement
Experience Anheuser-Busch InBev (AB InBev) Software Engineer Intern (July 2021 - present)
Creating impactful automation bots working with the ACoE team Working on new technologies like RPA-Blue Prism/AA, OCR ABBY, Chatbots, Python, C#, PowerApps etc.</description></item><item><title>Projects</title><link>https://ankithans.github.io/projects/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ankithans.github.io/projects/</guid><description>Here are some cool projects on which I worked upon.
CodeX https://github.com/ankithans/codeX Compile and Run your program and convert it into pseudocode. And Pseudocode itself can be converted into 118 global languages. Convert your code into Flow Chart and generate realtime code suggestions to imporve code quality as per industry standards Share your code with teachers, friends or colleagues as a unique URL on a single click Tech Stack - python, reactjs, pylint, tailwindcss, fastAPI, googleTrans, hackerearth API, SQLite3, pyflowchart Note Worthy https://github.</description></item><item><title>Archive</title><link>https://ankithans.github.io/archives/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ankithans.github.io/archives/</guid><description>archives</description></item></channel></rss>